Guide to the UE News Photograph Collection, 1933-1998 UE.14.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Individuals and Topics, 14.1.4.
  - Perkins, Frances: U.S. Sec of Labor (Box 27, Folder 75)
  - Potofsky, Jacob S.: Amalgamated Clothing Workers (Box 27, Folder 76)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 77)
  - Price, Gwilym: President Westinghouse (Box 27, Folder 78)
  - Proximire, William: Senator D-WI (Box 27, Folder 79)
  - Pucinski, Roman C.: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 80)
  - Rangel, Charles: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 81)
  - Rayburn, Samuel: Representative D-TX: Speaker of the House (Box 27, Folder 82)
  - Reece, Carroll B.: Representative R-TN (Box 27, Folder 83)
  - Reed, Daniel A.: Representative R-NY (Box 27, Folder 84)
  - Reuss, Henry S.: Representative D-WI (Box 27, Folder 85)
  - Reuther, Walter: UAW President (Box 27, Folder 86)
  - Rhodes, John J.: Representative R-AZ (Box 27, Folder 87)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham A.: Senator D-CT (Box 27, Folder 88)
  - Robinson, Reid: President Mine, Mill and Smelter (Box 27, Folder 89)
  - Robeson, Paul: Political Activist (Box 27, Folder 90)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor: Wife of U.S. President (Box 27, Folder 91)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Jr.: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 92)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Sr.: President of the U.S. (Box 27, Folder 93)
  - Roosevelt, James: Representative D-CA (Box 27, Folder 94)
  - Rosenberg, Alan: Attorney (Box 27, Folder 95)
  - Rosenblum, Frank: Amalgamated Clothing Workers Sec. Treas. (Box 27, Folder 96)
  - Rosenthal, Benjamin S.: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 97)
  - Russo, Marty: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 98)
  - Rostenkowski, Daniel: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 99)
  - Ryan, William F.: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 100)
  - Sabbath, Adolph: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 101)
  - Sadlak, Antoni N.: Representative R-CT (Box 27, Folder 102)
  - Sambo, John: IUE (Box 27, Folder 103)
  - Samuel, Howard: President IUD (Box 27, Folder 104)
  - Santora, William (Box 27, Folder 105)
  - Scanlon, Thomas: Representative D-PA (Box 27, Folder 106)
  - Scheneebeli, Herman T.: Representative R-PA (Box 27, Folder 107)
  - Schlieker, William N.: Nazi-Krupp Assistant (Box 27, Folder 108)
  - Schmidt, William: Mayor of Scranton, PA (Box 27, Folder 109)
  - Schoenbrun, David: Writer and Journalist (Box 27, Folder 110)
  - Schweiker, Richard S.: Representative R-PA (Box 27, Folder 111)
  - Scott, Hugh: Senator R-PA (Box 27, Folder 112)
  - Scranton, William W.: Senator R-PA (Box 27, Folder 113)
  - Shapley, Harlow: Scientist (Box 27, Folder 114)
  - Shapp, Milton: PA Governor (Box 27, Folder 115)
  - Sheehan, Timothy P.: Representative R-IL (Box 27, Folder 116)
  - Sheinkman, Jack: President ACTWU (Box 27, Folder 117)
  - Simon, Paul: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 118)
  - Smith, Alfred E.: NY Governor (Box 27, Folder 119)
  - Smith, Howard W.: Representative D-VA (Box 27, Folder 120)
  - Soloman, Saul: Doctor (Box 27, Folder 121)
  - Sparkman, John J.: Senator D-AL (Box 27, Folder 122)
  - Stafford, Robert T.: Senator R-VT (Box 27, Folder 123)
  - Steele, Robert H.: Representative R-CT (Box 27, Folder 124)
  - Steelman, John R.: U.S. Government Assistant to Truman (Box 27, Folder 125)
  - Stein, Herbert: Chairman Nixon Counsel: Eco. Adv. (Box 27, Folder 126)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E.: Senator D-IL (Box 27, Folder 127)
  - Stratton, Samuel S.: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 128)
  - Stokes, Louis: Representative D-OH (Box 27, Folder 129)
  - Sullivan, John: Representative D-MO (Box 27, Folder 130)
  - Sweeny, John: President SEIU (Box 27, Folder 131)
  - Taft, Robert: Senator R-OH (Box 27, Folder 132)
  - Taylor, Dean P.: Representative R-NY (Box 27, Folder 133)
  - Taylor, George W.: Professor and Author (Box 27, Folder 134)
  - Taylor, Glen: Senator D-ID: Progressive Party V.P. Candidate (Box 27, Folder 135)
  - Thomas, Elbert: Senator D-UT (Box 27, Folder 136)
  - Thomas, J. Parnell: Representative R-NJ (Box 27, Folder 137)
  - Thomas, R.J.: V.P. Auto Workers (Box 27, Folder 138)
  - Traficant, James: Representative D-OH (Box 27, Folder 139)
  - Thompson, Frank S. Jr.: Representative D-NJ (Box 27, Folder 140)
  - Tobey, Charles William: Senator R-NH (Box 27, Folder 141)
  - Truman, Harry S.: U.S. President (Box 27, Folder 142)
  - Tunney, John V.: Senator D-CA (Box 27, Folder 143)
  - Urey, Harold C.: Scientist (Box 27, Folder 144)
  - VanPelt, William K.: Representative R-WI (Box 27, Folder 145)
  - VanSlooten, John: UAW (Box 27, Folder 146)
  - Velde, Harold H.: Representative R-IL (Box 27, Folder 147)
  - Vigorito, Joseph P.: Representative D-PA (Box 27, Folder 148)
  - Wagner, Robert F.: Senator D-NY (Box 27, Folder 149)
  - Wald, George: Professor (Box 27, Folder 150)
  - Wallace, Henry: V.P. of U.S. (Box 27, Folder 151)
  - Washington, Harold: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 152)
  - Walter, Francis E.: Representative D-PA (Box 27, Folder 153)
  - Weaver, James D.: Representative D-PA (Box 27, Folder 154)
  - Wellstone, Paul: Senator D-MN (Box 27, Folder 155)
  - Whitney, A.F.: Bro. Railway Trainmen (Box 27, Folder 156)
  - Wier, Roy W.: Representative D-MN (Box 27, Folder 157)
  - Wiley, Alexander: Senator R-WI (Box 27, Folder 158)
  - William, Aubrey: President Southern Conf. Edu. Fund (Box 27, Folder 159)
  - Williams, Harrison A.: Senator D-NJ (Box 27, Folder 160)
  - Wilson, Charles: GM (Box 27, Folder 161)
  - Winpisinger, William: President IAM (Box 27, Folder 162)
  - Withrow, Gardner R.: Representative R-WI (Box 27, Folder 163)
  - Woffard, Harris: Senator D-PA (Box 27, Folder 164)
  - Wolcott, Jessee P.: Representative R-MI (Box 27, Folder 165)
  - Wolfe, Sidney: Doctor: Health Research Group (Box 27, Folder 166)
  - Wolfgang, Myra K.: Hotel and Restaurant Workers (Box 27, Folder 167)
  - Woodcock, Leonard: President UAW (Box 27, Folder 168)
  - Woodhouse, Chase Going: Representative (Box 27, Folder 169)
  - Wurf, Jerry: AFSCME President (Box 27, Folder 170)
  - Yates, Sidney: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 171)
  - Young, Stephen M.: Senator D-OH (Box 27, Folder 172)
  - Zablocki, Clement J.: Representative D-WI (Box 27, Folder 173)
  - AFL-CIO Leaders (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Abortion Lobby (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Albany Hearings, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Apartheid Demonstrations (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Fascist Parade (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Art (Murals) (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Automatic Screw Machine Company (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Automation (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Beauty Queens (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Black Workers (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Block Bork, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Boston Anti-Reaganomics Parade, August 1982 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Boycotts: Diamond Walnut and Clark Candy (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Bridgeport Rate Hike, July 1983 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - CBC-GE/W Negotiations, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - CBC-GE/W Negotiations, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - CBC Rally, June 1997 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - California Electronics Organizing Committee (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Campaign to End Wage Freeze, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 19-20)
  - Child Care Conference, New York (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Children: Demonstrating, Working, Playing (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Chile (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Citizen's Budget Campaign, May 1995 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Civil Rights Demonstration, Los Angeles, March 1989 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Civil Rights Struggle, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 26-28)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women: Founding Conference (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Coalition for a Safe Subway System (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Common Agenda Coalition (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Company Officials, 1940s-1960s (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Conference Board UE/W, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 34-35)
  - Conference Board UE-GE/W, 1970s-1980s (Box 28, Folder 36-37)
  - Conference Board GE, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Conference Board GE, 1970s-1980s (Box 28, Folder 39-40)
  - Conference Board GE, 1980s-1990s (Box 29, Folder 01-02)
  - Conferences: General, 1940s-1950s (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Conferences: General (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Conference: Erie (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Conference: Washington, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - CIO: Meetings, Members, General (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Congress (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Congress Investigations: House Labor, HUAC, etc. (Box 29, Folder 09-10)
  - Congress Progress Caucus, January 1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Congressman (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Copeland Refrigerator Workers, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Crowds (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Cutting Tool Conferences, 1980, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Deborah Hospital (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Debs, Eugene (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Defense of UE (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Delegation on Take Away: PA Legislature: Districts 1 and 6, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Demonstrations: Miscellaneous and Contact Prints (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Department Store Employee Union, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Dewald Organizing Committee, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Directories of Congress People (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Echlin Rally, December 1997 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - El Salvador (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Energy Crisis, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Entertainment Pictures WWII (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - ERA March, April 1989 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Erie Automation Robotics Conference, May 1984 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Erie County Labor Congress Conference (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - European Unions (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - FDR and ERA Prominent Figures (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - FDR Memorial (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - FE Fights Layoff, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - FE Staff (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - FEPC Campaign, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Factories (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Fair Employment Practices Committee (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Fair Practices Committee of UE (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Families/Family Life (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Farmers-Migratory Workers and Other Non-Industrial Workers (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Fascists-Nazis (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Federal Supreme Court, 1930s-1960s (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - For German Exhibit: Strikes, All Districts, All Years (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Foreign Trade Unions-Meeting with Officials, December 1986 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - France-CGT (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - GE: General Electric (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - GE Conference Board, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - GE Conference Board, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - GE Conference Board, 1960s (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - GE Conference Board General and GE Conference Board, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - GE Contract Signing, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - GE International Harvesters Conference, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - GE Lamp Conference, 1951, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - GE Negotiations, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 09-10)
  - GE Negotiations, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - GE Negotiations, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - GE Negotiations, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - GE Negotiations, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - GE Salary Organization Committee, Pittsfield (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - GE Strike, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
  - GE Strike Ratification/Vote, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - GE Trial, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - GE Wage Conference, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - GEB: Contact Prints (Box 30, Folder 21-22)
  - GEB: Meetings (Box 30, Folder 23-24)
  - GM: General Motors (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - GM Conference Board, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - General Executive Board, 1930s-1940s (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - General Cable, 1st National Contract with UE (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - General Officers with Labor Leaders (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - General Officers with Staff, 1940s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - General Officers, Founding Officers (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - General Officers, Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - "Ghetto Life" (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Guatemala (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Haiti (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Harrisburg Blitz (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Harvest Strike Scenes (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Harvester: UE at Congressional Farm Hearings, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Health Care Rallies, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Health, Medical, Diseases, Accidents (Box 31, Folder 01-02)
  - Hearings: Job, Senate Labor Reform, Congressional (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - High Treason (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Historical Labor Figures/ Events (Box 31, Folder 05-08)
  - Hoover (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Housing: Strikes and Demonstrations (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - IUE: International Union of Electrical Workers (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - IUE and Other Raiders (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Empty (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - IAM: International Association of Machinists (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - International Harvester, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - International Longshoremen and Warehousemen's Union (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - International Metalworkers Federation (Box 31, Folder 17-18)
  - Inquiring Photographer (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - International Economic Conversion (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Jenson Company Shop, Los Angeles (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Job Training (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Labor Assembly for Peace Conference, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Labor for Peace Conference, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Labor Law Reform Demonstration, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Labor Notes, September 19-20, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Labor Research Association (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Labor Rights Rally, Chicago-New Bedford, February 1990 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Labor Rights Tour, February 1994 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Labor Solidarity: Greyhound Workers (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Labor Solidarity: Harper and Rowe (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Labor Solidarity: J.P. Stevens (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Labor Solidarity: Local 111, I.B.T. (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Labor Solidarity: Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Labor Solidarity: New Party Meetings (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Labor Solidarity: PATCO (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Leon Mohill speaks to UERMWA, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Lincoln, Abraham (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Lobby Week, March 28-April 2, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Local Union Officers, Business Agent, Staff (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Lynn Campaign: Local 201, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - MICA (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Machinery (Box 31, Folder 43-45)
  - March and Rally for Miners, Pittsburgh, PA, August 1989 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - March for the Homeless, Washington D.C., October 1989 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - March for Justice and Peace, Washington D.C., 1985 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - March on Washington, August 1983 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - McCarthy Hearings at GE: Schenectady and Lynn, MA (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Meetings with Legislative Representatives (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Meetings, general (non-strike) (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Mervin Wave Clip Company, Buffalo, New York, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Migratory Workers (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers Union (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Mine Safety Workers Strike, Pittsburgh (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Minimum Wage Rally, October 29, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous U.S. Presidents and Historical Figures (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Miss Negro Victory Workers (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Mobilize for Women's Lives, November 1989 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - National Defense, UE Metal Shortages Conference (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - National Healthcare Ambulance Drive, Fall 1991 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - National Healthcare, June 1991 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - National Healthcare, October 1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - National Healthcare Town Meetings, January 1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - NLRB: National Labor Relations Board (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - National Rank and File Conference, Chicago, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - National Trade Union Rank and File Conference, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Negotiations: Contact Prints, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Negotiations GE/W Service Workers, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Negro Exhibit, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - New Comer Products Company (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - New York City Scenes (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - New York Compensation Board, UE New York Conference Board, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Empty (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper/Radio (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Nicaragua (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Not Bread Alone Conference, New York, November 9, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Nuclear Industry (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - OPA Petition Rally, 1940s (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Occupational Safety and Health, "Hamlet", 1990s (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Orange County Workers/ Justice/ Democracy, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Organizing, 1990s (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Organizing Committee, Ward Leonard Electric Company (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Outdoor Columns: Fred Goetz (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Outdoor Columns: Fred Peterson (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Parades, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Peace Demonstration, New York, December 1982 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Peace Rally, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Peace Protests Worldwide, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Pensioners General (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Pension Hearings, 1973, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - People's Progress Convention, August 1992 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Phelps Dodge: Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Chicago, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Philco Conference (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Picket Lines: General, 1940s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Picket Lines District 1 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Picket Lines District 2, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Picket Lines District 3 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Picket Lines District 4, 1940s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Picket Lines District 6, 1940s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Picket Lines District 11, 1940s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Picket Lines A.S.R., 1940s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Empty (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Picket Lines Anti-Stuyvesant Evictions (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Picket Lines Schenectady (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Picket Lines Tung-sol (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Pittsburgh Blitz, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Plant Closings, 1960s-1990s (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Plants-Workers (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Plastics, 1980s-1990s (Box 32, Folder 52-53)
  - Police Violence (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Police Violence in East Pittsburgh in 1916 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Political Action: District 1 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Political Action: District 2 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Political Action: District 3 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Political Action: District 4 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - Political Action: District 6 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Political Action: District 7 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Political Action: District 8 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - Political Action: District 9 (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Political Action: District 11 (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Political Action: Albany Delegation (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Political Action: Farmer Aid (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Political Action: General (Box 32, Folder 67-69)
  - Political Action: PAC (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Political Action: Taft-Hartley (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Pollution (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Porcelain Workers (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Poverty (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Press Conference, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Press Conference on Wage Drive with James Matles (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Products (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Production Awards (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Production Conference, Indiana, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Progressive Party National Convention, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Publicity Conference, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Racist Terror (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - RCA Organizing Committee, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Radiation-Japan (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Radio Broadcast/Conference, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Radio Report on Negotiations, District 4, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Railroads (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Railroad Demonstration, Washington D.C., April, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Rally Against U.S. Intervention in Central America, March 24, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Rally for Peace, Jobs, and Justice in Washington D.C., April 1985 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Raytheon Organizing Committee Dance, September 1943 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Re-Conversion (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Recipe Exchange, April 1972 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Recreation: General (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Recreation Room: Salsa League, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Religious Leader Rabbi Abba Hillel Silver (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Remington-Rand, Johnson City (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Republic of Ireland (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Retirees, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Rex Manufacturing Company (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Rhode Island Blitz, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Roosevelt, F.D. (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Runaway Plants: Wilson and Company (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Salaried Workers (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Science/Research (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Schools/College Students (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Ships (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Shorter Work Week, 1970s (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Singer Sewing Machine, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Senate Labor Committee Hearings, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Skilled Trade Conference, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Smith and Wesson, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Social Security, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Solidarity Day, Washington D.C. Rally, August, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - South Africa (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - South East Asia and Vietnam (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Soviet Trade Unionists, 1980s (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Soviet Trade Union Delegation to U.S., June 1978 (Box 33, Folder 48-49)
  - Springfield Machine Tool Conference, December 1983 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Speed-Up, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Stand for Truth Lobby, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Stanley Campaign, Waynesboro, VA, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Stills from Hollywood and Other Commercial Films (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Stills from "It's a Wonderful Life" (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Strikes Newspaper Articles, 1916 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Strikes District 11, 1930s (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Strikes A.S.R. Workers, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Strikes Truck Drivers, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Strikes Philco, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Strikes Ohio Brass, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Strikes General, 1930s-1940s (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Strikes District 1, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 08-09)
  - Strikes District 2, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Strikes District 2, Local 282, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Strikes District 3, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Strikes District 4, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Strikes District 4, Local 404, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Strikes District 5, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Strikes District 6, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Strikes District 6, Local 601, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Empty (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Strikes District 7, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Strikes District 7, Local 801, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Strikes District 9, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Strikes District 10, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Strikes District 11, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Strikes, National Vote, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Strikes, Phelps Dodge, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Strikes, Conferences, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Strike General, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 27-28)
  - Strikes Warren, OH, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Strikes Miscellaneous, 1950s (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Strikes Aid UE Mine Workers, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Strikes Harvester Workers, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Strikes U.A.W., 1954 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Strikes District 1, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Strikes District 1, Local 107, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Strikes District 2, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Strikes District 4, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Strikes District 6, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Strikes District 11, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Strikes General, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Strikes Music Hall, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Strikes I.R.C. Local 105 (Box 34, Folder 42)